cute
可愛い
...
Erotic...
エ ロい...
エロい...
How to grow erotic
生 え 方 エロ
Yes
い ね
...
amazing...
すごい...
The way it grows is erotic
生え方エロい
hey...
ね...
Erotic...
エロい...
Chin Chin...
ちんちん...
amazing...
すごい...
It didn't fly...
飛 ばなかった...
Did you see it just now?
今、見ました?
What happened?
何が出たの?
Too erotic...
エロすぎて...
Just looking at it now...
今、見てるだけで...
You didn't touch it, did you?
触ってなかったよね、
now...
今...
I was just looking at it, now...
見てるだけでいっちゃった、今...
Too erotic...
エロすぎて...
It's flying here too...
ここにも飛んでるじゃん...
Hey?
ねえ?
Did it take?
かかった?
Is it not working?
かかってない?
It feels so good there
あ そこめっちゃ気持ちいい
...
Can you taste the taste?
せ じの味する?
Open your legs.
足開いてもらお
cormorant...
う...
It came out, but...
出ちゃったけど...
It's totally frivolous though
全然キンキンなんだけど
...
It feels so good...
す っげー気持ちいい...
Oh, that's terrible...
あ、やばい...
wait a minute...
ちょっと待って...
It's out...
出ちゃった...
There's a lot in the food...
お餌に入ってるいっぱい...
amazing...
すごい...
It's the whole face...
全顔だよ...
I'm angry
怒です
...
I'm angry...
怒 です...
I'm not satisfied at all...
全然満足されてない...
Because...
だって...
It was impossible.
無理だったんだもん
...
Why does it feel so good to have a pussy like this?
なん でこんなまんこめって気持ちいいの?
I don't know...
わかんない...
terrible...
やばい...
It feels so good
す っ ごい気持ちいい
...
terrible...
や ばい...
That's amazing, I guess...
すごいね、やっぱ...
The waist...
腰遣いが...
It's just as you imagine.
想像してる通りだね
...
Amazing movement...
すごい 動き...
Let me open your legs...
足開いてもらおう...
Press your hand...
手を押して...
Put your feet up...
足を立てて...
Give me your hand...
手をくれ...
Even if you put your foot out...
足を出しても...
So great
すっげーえらい
...
Look this way...
こ っち向いて...
Great
えらい
...
amazing...
すごい...
Take it out...
出して...
I took it out about 3 times...
3回くらい出しちゃった...